Stephen J. Gould papers M1437
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - Subseries: Incoming Letters, 1982-1987
    - Dewey, Robert D. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Da (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - De (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - De (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Di (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Do (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Do (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Dr - Ds (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Du - Dy (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Edgerton, Samuel (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Eldredge, Niles (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Ea - Ec (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Ed - Eh (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Ei - El (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Em - Ep (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Er - Ey (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - E Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Feldman, Marcus W. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Ferguson, Evan R. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Freeman, Ruth (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Fa (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Fe (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Fi (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Fl (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Fo (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Fr (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Fr - Fu (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Aldrich, Michele (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Susan E. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Galloway, Jean (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Gazzaniga, Michael S. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Gilinsky, Norman L. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Goldstein, Sydney (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Ga (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Ge - Gh (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Gi (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Gi - Gl (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Go (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Go (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Go (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Gr (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Gr (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Gr (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Gr - Gy (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Hallam, Anthony (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Hanson, F. Allan (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Harnad, Stevan (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Harrar, Linda (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Hickman, Carole S. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Ha (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Ha (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - He (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - He (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - He - Hi (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Hi - Hl (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Ho (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Ho (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Ho - Hs (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Hu - Hy (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - I (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Jablonski, David (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Ja (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Je (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Jo (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Jo - Ju (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - J Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Katz, Bob (K & S Speakers) (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Kauffman, Erle G. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Kauffman, Marvin E. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, Henry C. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - King, David G. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Kurtz, Paul (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Kwok, John (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Ka (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Ka (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Ke (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Ki (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Ki (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Kl - Kn (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Ko (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Kr (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Ku - Ky (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Levy, Marion J., Jr. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Linn, Fran Ford (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - La (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - La (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Le (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Le (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Li (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Ll - Lo (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Lo - Ly (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Margulis, Lynn (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Martinez, Lee Anne (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Mayr, Ernst (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - McElroy, Michael B. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - McKinney, Michael L. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Mendelsohn, Everett (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Merton, Robert (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Milkman, Roger (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Miller, Tom (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Milner, Richard (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Montagu, Ashley (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Musgrave, Peggy B. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Ma (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Ma (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Ma (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Ma (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Mc (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Mc (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Me (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Me (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Mi (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Mi (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Mo (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Mo (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Mo (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Mu - My (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - M Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Neusner, Jacob (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Newell, Norman D. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Nicholson, Thomas D. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Nitecki, Matthew H. (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Novik, Jack D. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Na (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Ne (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Ni (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - No - Nu (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - N Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Ob - Oj (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Ol - On (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Op - Os (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Ot - Oz (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Paynter, R. A., Jr. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Pojeta, John, Jr. (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Pollack, Alan (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Press, Michelle (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Proctor, Robert (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Puckette, Linda (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Purcell, Edward M. (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Pa (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Pa (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Pe (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Pe - Ph (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Pi (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Pl (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Po (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Pr (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Pt - Py (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Rappaport, Rhoda (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Raup, David M. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Reynolds, Wayne R. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Rice, Joseph (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Richards, Bob (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Rogin, Gilbert L. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Rosen, Walter G. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Rosenthal, Arthur J. (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Roth, Michael S. (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Rudwick, Martin J. S. (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Ruse, Michael (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Ra (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Re (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Rh - Ri (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Ro (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Ro (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Ru - Ry (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Sagan, Carl (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Sanders, Jack T. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Schierenberg, D. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Schwartz, Sally R. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Searchinger, Gene (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Selden, Steven (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Sepkoski, J. John, Jr. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Shapiro, Judith (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Shekerjian, Denise (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Sibatani, Atuhiro (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Sibley, Charles G. (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Signor, Philip W. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Silver, Bob (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Skinner, B. F. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Slavkin, Harold C. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Spence, A. Michael (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Stebbins, G. Ledyard (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Stevens, Katharine F. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Sturm, Lois M. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Swann, Christopher K.; Swann, H. K.; Swann A. H. S. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Sa (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Sc (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Sc (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Se (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Sh (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Sh (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Si (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Sk - Sl (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Sm (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Sn - Sp (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - So (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - St (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - St (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Su (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Sw - Sy (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Tee, Garry J. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Tillier, Simon (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Tobach, Ethel (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Tomasson, Gunnar (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Tripp, Edward (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Turekian, Karl K. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Ta (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Te (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Th (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Ti - To (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Tr (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Ts - Ty (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - U (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - van Helden, Albert (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - VanValen, Leigh M. (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Verdon, Andrew J., Jr. (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Va (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Ve - Vr (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Ward, Peter (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Wassersug, Richard (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Watson, Reid (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Watson, Signe Warner (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Wesling, Donald (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - West, Robert M. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - West-Eberhard, Mary Jane (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Wheeler, Harvey (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Wheldon & Wesley Limited (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - White, Clyde S. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Whitla, Dean K. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Wilde, Benna B. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Ellen W. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Willis, Delta (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Winter, Gabriel (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Wyllie, Peter J. (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Wa (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Wa (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - We (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - We (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Wh (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Wi (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Wi (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Wo (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Wr - Wy (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - W Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Yates, F. Eugene (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Yellin, Lori (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Young, J. M. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Yu, Xiaobo (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Yunis, Edmond (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Ya - Yu (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Zenger, Donald H. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Za - Zy (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Y - Z Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Family & Unidentified (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Subseries: Incoming Letters, Bulk, 1986-1989; 1985-1989
    - Abrams, Susan E. (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Aretakis, Jonathan (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Aa - Al (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Am - Ap (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Ar - Az (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - A Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Barber, Edwin (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Barnes, Robert D. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Bartel, Brad (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Bell, Michael A. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Belton, Neil (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Blom, Benjamin (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Boyer, Howard (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Brodie, H. Keith H. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Butler, James N. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Ba (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Be (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Bi - Bo (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Br (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Br (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Bu - By (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - B Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Cullenberg, Stephen (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Ca (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Ch - Ci (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Cl (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Co (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Cr - Cz (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Durant, John R. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Da (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - De - Di (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Dj - Do (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Dr - Dw (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - E (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Fagen, Robert (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Fort, Deborah C. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Friedberg, Lionel (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Fa - Fe (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Fi - Fl (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Fo (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Fr - Fu (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Gilinsky, Norman (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Gillespie, Margaret (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Golden, William T. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Guskin, Alan E. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Ga (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Ge - Gi (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Gl - Go (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Gr - Gw (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Ha (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - He (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Hi - Hy (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - K & S Speakers (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Kang, Won-Yong (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Kelly, Allan O. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Kinnel, R. B. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Kwok, John (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Ka (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Ke - Kj (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Kl - Ky (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Leake, B. E. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Lewis, Susan W. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Lincoln, Tim (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - La (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Le (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Li - Ly (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Mayr, Ernst (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - McElroy, Michael B. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Mendelsohn, Everett (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Montagu, Ashley (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Morohishi, Kazuo (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Ma (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Ma (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Mc - Me (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Mi - Mo (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Mu - My (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Subseries: Incoming Letters, 1963-1974
    - Abbott, R. Tucker (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Addicott, Warren O. (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Aleu, M. Olga (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Alexander, R. McNeill (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Garland E. (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Ab - Ay (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - A Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Beers, John R. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Bock, Walter (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Bretsky, Peter W. and Sara S. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Ba - Be (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Bi - By (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - B Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Chappell, John E., Jr. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Chastain, Murray (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Clark, George R., II (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Cock, Alan (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Cohen, Ralph (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Cracraft, Joel (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Crompton, A. W. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Ca - Cl (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Co - Cu (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - C Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Dodson, Peter (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Dunlop, John T. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Da - Du (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Eldredge, Niles (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Emmott, Margaret (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Ea - Ey (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - E Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Fox, H. Munro (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Freeman, William H. (Freeman, Cooper & Co.) (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Fa - Fr (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Goss, Richard J. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Gould, Leonard and Eleanor (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Greiner, Gary O. G. and Betty (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Greene, John C. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Ga - Gu (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Hallam, Anthony (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Halsell, Grace (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Hyami, Haru (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Ha - Hu (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Imbrie, John (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - I (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Jefferies, R. P. S. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Jerrison, Harry J. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Ralph G. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Johnston, Richard F. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Ja - Jo (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - J Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Kaesler, Roger L. (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Kidwell, James F. (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Kier, Porter M. (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Kokshaysky, N. V. (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Ka - Ku (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Lewis, Harlan (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Livingston, Katherine (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - La - Ly (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Mackenzie, Fred T. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Macurda, Donald B., Jr. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Mayr, Ernst (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Mendelsohn, Everett (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Merriam, Daniel F. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Ma - Mc (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Me - My (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - M Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Nelson, Clifford M. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Nelson, Gareth J. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Nevo, Eviatar (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Newell, Norman D. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Newton, John (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Na - Ny (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Oliver, William A., Jr. (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Ostrom, John H. (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Oa - Ox (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Peisch, Mark L. (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Piip, Leida (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Pa - Pr (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Q (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Radinsky, Len (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Raup, David M. (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Ray, D. Michael (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Reese, David S. (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Reyment, Richard (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Rolfe, W. D. I. (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Rowell, A. J. (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Rudwick, Martin J. S. (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Ra - Ru (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Sagan, Carl (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Schopf, Thomas J. M. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Sepkoski, Jack (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Simpson, George Gaylord (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Solbrig, Otto T. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Sokal, Robert R. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Stanley, Steven M. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Stebbins, G. Ledyard (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Sa - Sl (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Sm - Sz (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Thayer, Charles W. (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, Roger D. K. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Thompson, Ida (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Torrens, Hugh (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Ta - Ty (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - U (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Van Valen, Leigh (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Vermeij, Geerat J. (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Va - Vo (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - V Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Wa - Wy (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - W Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Y (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Zinn, Donald J. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Z (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - X, Y, Z Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Subseries: Incoming Letters, 1989-1993
    - Ob - Ox (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Perry, Leslie G. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Pa - Pe (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Pi - Pu (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Q (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Rockman, Alexis (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Rogovin, Milton (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Ro - Ry (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Ra - Ri (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Sagan, Carl (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Schierenberg, Dieter (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Sibley, Charles (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Suchard, Marc A. (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Sykes, Christopher (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Sa (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Sc - Se (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Sh - Sl (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Sm - Sq (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - St - Sw (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Ta - Ty (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Va - Vu (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - V Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Wa (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - We - Wi (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Wo - Wu (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Z (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Subseries: Incoming Letters, 1990-1997
    - Anderson, Wyatt W. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Aa - Ae (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Ag - Al (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Am - Ap (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Ar (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - As - Au (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - A Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Baker, Robert J. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Belton, Neil (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Bintliff, John (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Blake, Carl David (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Block, Laurie (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Boss, Kenneth J. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Breguet, Georges (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Brockman, John (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Peter G. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Broxon, Duane (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Bryant, Ruth A. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Bunge, William (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Burgess, Kathryn H. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Burns, Joan Simpson (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Burns, Ken (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Butler, Syd (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Ba (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Ba (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Ba (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Be (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Be (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Bi - Bj (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Bl (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Bo (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Br (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Br (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Bu (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Bu (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - B Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Claudine (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Corman, Cid (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Courtright, Frederick T. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Ca (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Ce - Cha (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Che - Ci (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Cl (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Co (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Cr - Cz (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - C Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Darby, Grace (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Debus, Allen A. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Dershowitz, Alan M. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Dover, Gabriel A. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Da (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Da (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - De (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Di - Dj (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Do (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Dr - Dy (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Elder, David (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Ea - Ed (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Eg - Ek (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - El - En (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Er - Ey (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Fabian, Andy (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Fazio, Russ (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Fellows, John (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Ferguson, Evan R. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Fern, Alan (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Foote, Mike (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Freedle, Roy (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Fa (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Fe (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Fi (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Fl (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Fo (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Fu (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Fra (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Fre - Fry (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Gates, Henry Louis, Jr. (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Gee, Henry (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Golden, William T. (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Goldmark, Peter C., Jr. (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Gould, Stephen Jay (To Agnes Pilot) (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Guerrero, Ricardo (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Ga (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Ge - Gh (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Gi - Gl (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Go (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Go (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Gr (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Gu - Gw (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Hannibal, Joseph (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Harlowe, Joan (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Horowitz, Paul (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Houff, S. A. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Hab - Hal (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Ham - Han (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Har (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Has - Hay (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Hea - Hen (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Her - Hey (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Hi (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Hoa - Hol (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Hom - How (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Hu - Hy (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - I (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Ja (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Je (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Jo - Ju (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Katz, Bob (K & S Speakers) (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Kuralt, Charles (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Kutscheid, Timothy (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Ka (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Ke (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Kh - Ki (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Kj - Kn (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Ko - Kr (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Ku - Ky (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Lee, Paula Y. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Levy-Leblond, Jean-Marc (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Lewis, Susan W. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - La (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Le (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Le (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Li (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Ll - Ly (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Machol, Robert E. (Box 68, Folder 6)